{
  "id": "flashcard-kanji-number",
  "title": "Đếm Ngày & Tháng",
  "description": "Luyện tập từ vựng: Ngày & Tháng.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "1日",
      "answer": "mùng 1",
      "speak": "tsuitachi"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "2日",
      "answer": "mùng 2, 2 ngày",
      "speak": "futsuka"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "3日",
      "answer": "mùng 3, 3 ngày",
      "speak": "mikka"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "4日",
      "answer": "mùng 4, 4 ngày",
      "speak": "yokka"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "5日",
      "answer": "mùng 5, 5 ngày",
      "speak": "itsuka"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "6日",
      "answer": "mùng 6, 6 ngày",
      "speak": "muika"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "7日",
      "answer": "mùng 7, 7 ngày",
      "speak": "nanoka"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "8日",
      "answer": "mùng 8, 8 ngày",
      "speak": "youka"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "9日",
      "answer": "mùng 9, 9 ngày",
      "speak": "kokonoka"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "10日",
      "answer": "mùng 10, 10 ngày",
      "speak": "tooka"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "1月",
      "answer": "tháng 1",
      "speak": "ichigatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "2月",
      "answer": "tháng 2",
      "speak": "nigatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "3月",
      "answer": "tháng 3",
      "speak": "sangatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "4月",
      "answer": "tháng 4",
      "speak": "shigatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "5月",
      "answer": "tháng 5",
      "speak": "gogatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "6月",
      "answer": "tháng 6",
      "speak": "rokugatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "7月",
      "answer": "tháng 7",
      "speak": "shichigatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "8月",
      "answer": "tháng 8",
      "speak": "hachigatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "9月",
      "answer": "tháng 9",
      "speak": "kugatsu"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "10月",
      "answer": "tháng 10",
      "speak": "juugatsu"
    }
  ]
}